[{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678902479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":13752,"timeElapsed":92194},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678922240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":19758,"timeElapsed":111956},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678931392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":9149,"timeElapsed":121108},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678937085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":5689,"timeElapsed":126800},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678941404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4317,"timeElapsed":131120},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678950376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":8969,"timeElapsed":140092},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5763,"timeElapsed":145857},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678966743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":10599,"timeElapsed":156459},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6544,"timeElapsed":163004},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678992972,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":18147,"timeElapsed":182688},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7636,"timeElapsed":190326},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5771,"timeElapsed":196100},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679021643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":15255,"timeElapsed":211358},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679026880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5236,"timeElapsed":216596},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":7039,"timeElapsed":223638},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679041513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":7589,"timeElapsed":231229},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679050810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":9294,"timeElapsed":240526},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679055708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4896,"timeElapsed":245424},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":20494,"timeElapsed":267901},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":13247,"timeElapsed":281148},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679095552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4117,"timeElapsed":285268},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099190,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3637,"timeElapsed":288906},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":292568},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679107173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4318,"timeElapsed":296889},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679111166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3992,"timeElapsed":300882},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4680,"timeElapsed":305563},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3998,"timeElapsed":309564},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":13310,"timeElapsed":324331},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679138784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":4165,"timeElapsed":328500},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679143423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4637,"timeElapsed":333139},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679147085,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3659,"timeElapsed":336801},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5568,"timeElapsed":342371},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3716,"timeElapsed":346089},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3190,"timeElapsed":349281},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2770,"timeElapsed":352053},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679164807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"204","question":"Is there a person or are there people in your life that you call regularly to check up on? How often do you call them and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2468,"timeElapsed":354523},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169816,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4030,"timeElapsed":359531},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3084,"timeElapsed":362618},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679182676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9773,"timeElapsed":372392},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186013,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3334,"timeElapsed":375729},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679188746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2730,"timeElapsed":378462},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":4300,"timeElapsed":382764},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2809,"timeElapsed":385575},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679200015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4154,"timeElapsed":389731},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3403,"timeElapsed":393137},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679210670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6398,"timeElapsed":400386},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679213089,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2416,"timeElapsed":402805},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2724,"timeElapsed":405531},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679222415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":6598,"timeElapsed":412131},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3324,"timeElapsed":415458},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3242,"timeElapsed":418701},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679231989,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3002,"timeElapsed":421705},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235147,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3156,"timeElapsed":424863},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679237419,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"218","question":"Is there a food that you would feel comfortable eating for lunch every day for the rest of your life? What is it? Where did you first have this food?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":427135},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679251734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":12396,"timeElapsed":441450},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679254360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2625,"timeElapsed":444075},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679257412,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3049,"timeElapsed":447127},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679261471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":451187},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679268784,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7311,"timeElapsed":458500},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679273877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5091,"timeElapsed":463593},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679280311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6432,"timeElapsed":470027},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679282848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2535,"timeElapsed":472564},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679286533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3685,"timeElapsed":476249},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679288739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"120","question":"If you met with your 17 year-old self, would the younger you like the current you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2204,"timeElapsed":478454},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679303932,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":14086,"timeElapsed":493648},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679309353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":5421,"timeElapsed":499069},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679314140,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":4785,"timeElapsed":503856},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679320325,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6183,"timeElapsed":510041},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679324783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4457,"timeElapsed":514499},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679329726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4941,"timeElapsed":519442},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679336351,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6622,"timeElapsed":526067},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679339102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2749,"timeElapsed":528818},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679341749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2645,"timeElapsed":531465},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679344622,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"84","question":"What would you want to be swallowed by? What would you most want to drown in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2871,"timeElapsed":534338},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679357286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8966,"timeElapsed":547002},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679359899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2610,"timeElapsed":549615},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679363146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3245,"timeElapsed":552862},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679368101,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4953,"timeElapsed":557817},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679371223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3120,"timeElapsed":560939},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679373568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2341,"timeElapsed":563284},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679375802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2231,"timeElapsed":565517},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679378486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2682,"timeElapsed":568201},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679380624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2137,"timeElapsed":570340},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679392543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":10756,"timeElapsed":582258},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679394828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2282,"timeElapsed":584544},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679403601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8771,"timeElapsed":593317},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":10871,"timeElapsed":604191},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679418177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3701,"timeElapsed":607893},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679423970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5789,"timeElapsed":613686},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679427071,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3099,"timeElapsed":616787},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679429476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2401,"timeElapsed":619192},{"subjectID":"yc85b7w41f","prolificID":"67661c967444fe3b3522bf6e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b35362bb989a70f1c6f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4722,"timeElapsed":623915}]